{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"9795/13",
			"answer":"9795/13",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"8727/25",
			"answer":"8727/25",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"6458/57",
			"answer":"6458/57",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1971/72",
			"answer":"1971/72",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2892/12",
			"answer":"2892/12",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"18.17/0.79",
			"answer":"18.17/0.79",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"5890/6.2",
			"answer":"5890/6.2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"172.9/0.91",
			"answer":"172.9/0.91",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"50.16/0.88",
			"answer":"50.16/0.88",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"6110/0.65",
			"answer":"6110/0.65",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}